General information

Benjamin Alexander Windsor 11/06/1994 (+44) 7748 472708 benjaminwindsor.com benjaminawindsor@gmail.com



Personal information

I'm a creative digital designer currently residing in London. My experience spans across both digital and web. I'm affluent in the Adobe creative suite specifically Ai, Ps, Id & Xd alongside a strong understanding of front end languages html5, css3, and source control systems such as Git. I work to create pleasant visual experiences with user centric design always at the forefront.

Skills and abilities

Excellent coding

Adobe creative suite

High understanding of UI/UX

A keen eye for design

Versatile and adaptable

Final Cut Pro

Education

University:

Graduated with a 2.1 in Creative Media Technology from Leeds Beckett University - July 2015

College:

BTEC National Diploma in Interactive Media - Graded Merit BTEC National Certificate in Creative Media - Graded Pass

School:

11 GCSE's A* - C including English & Maths

Relevant Experience

Digital Designer - Vanarama - May 2021 - Present

Digital Design Recruitment Consultant - Major Players - September 2019 - September 2020

Junior Front End Web Dev - Hastings Direct - September 2017 - February 2018

Interests

Outside of work I like to over indulge in drinking coffee. I also enjoy creating music and Illustrations along with watching Formula 1, Uber rating 4.9.